const tasksSelect = [
  {
    id: 1,
    translate: 'Это было действительно важно?',
    question: '___ it really important',
    variant1: 'Was',
    variant2: 'were',
    variant3: 'is',
    variant4: 'are',
    correct: 'Was',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    translate: 'Ты был дейсвтительно уверен',
    question: '___ you really sure',
    variant1: 'was',
    variant2: 'Were',
    variant3: 'is',
    variant4: 'are',
    correct: 'Were',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    translate: 'Это было лучше?',
    question: '___ it better?',
    variant1: 'Was',
    variant2: 'were',
    variant3: 'is',
    variant4: 'are',
    correct: 'Was',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    translate: 'Когда ты был там последний раз ',
    question: '___ ___ you there last time?',
    variant1: 'When was',
    variant2: 'When were',
    variant3: 'Where was',
    variant4: 'Where were',
    correct: 'When were',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    translate: 'Ты был занят вчера,',
    question: '___ you busy yesterday?',
    variant1: 'was',
    variant2: 'Were',
    variant3: 'is',
    variant4: 'are',
    correct: 'Were',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    translate: 'Это было проблемой для тебя?',
    question: '___ it a problem for you?',
    variant1: 'was',
    variant2: 'were',
    variant3: 'is',
    variant4: 'are',
    correct: 'was',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    translate: 'Почему это было так дорого?',
    question: '___ ___ it so expensive?',
    variant1: 'Why was',
    variant2: 'Why were',
    variant3: 'How was',
    variant4: 'How were',
    correct: 'Why was',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    translate: 'Что было на столе?',
    question: '___',
    variant1: 'What was on the ceiling?',
    variant2: 'What was on the desk?',
    variant3: 'What was on the table?',
    variant4: 'What was on the floor?',
    correct: 'What was on the table?',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    translate: 'Как ты скачал эту программу',
    question: '___',
    variant1: 'How did you downloaded this program?',
    variant2: 'When did you downloaded this program?',
    variant3: 'When did you download this program?',
    variant4: 'How did you download this program?',
    correct: 'How did you download this program?',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    translate: '',
    question: '___',
    variant1: 'Why was it so slow?',
    variant2: 'Why was it so fast?',
    variant3: 'Why were it so fast?',
    variant4: 'Why were it so slow?',
    correct: 'Why was it so slow?',
  },
];

export default tasksSelect;
